For the next step, let's do an exercise that focuses
on extracting out the value of one of those attributes. We're
going to do this exercise a little bit differently. You'll implement this
on the Udacity platform. And we'll be able to verify that
your code is correct. After this video, you'll see an IDE
like this. Where it contains some starter code, as well as
some j unit tests in a separate tab. In particular, we
want you to implement this function, to get the max temperature
for a day. You're given a weather JSON
string, formatted the same way as you would get
from the Open Weather Map service. And you
also get the day index that we care about.
Feel free to play around with the code
in Android Studio, or a separate development environment, before
you paste your answer here. Or you can use
the Udacity IDE. Whichever feels more natural to you.